bonbast.com 2019-11-18

# Privacy Policy - Bonbast.com

#### Privacy Policy for www.bonbast.com

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at info@bonbast.com.

At www.bonbast.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.bonbast.com and how it is used. Please note that this Policy may be amended from time to time and that any changes will be published here. 

#### Log Files

Like many other Web sites, www.bonbast.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

#### Cookies and Web Beacons

www.bonbast.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.   

####  Cookies are used for the following purposes: 

**Settings within the Website**

These cookies are used to save your settings; allowing you to hide information boxes you have become familiar with, etc. 

**Google Analytics & Interest-Based Online Advertising**

This website uses Google Analytics. Google Analytics uses “cookies” to help us analyze how visitors use the site. The information collected includes the pages a visitor visits, the time a visit occurred, whether the visitor has been to the site before and what site referred the visitor to the web page. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information on behalf of www.Bonbast.com to evaluate your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity. We also use Google Analytics' 3 rd -party audience data, such as age, gender and interests to better understand the behavior of our customers and provide advertising targeted to suit your preferences and interests. For example, you may see ads on the Google Display Network, based on information collected through automated means (such as cookies). Automated technologies are used to collect information when you click on our ads, which helps track and manage the effectiveness of our marketing efforts. You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the [Google Ad Preferences Page](https://www.google.com/settings/ads) and if you want you can opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings or by using this [Google tool](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) . 

**Remarketing on the Website and App**

 Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to www.bonbast.com or other websites.  
 Google's use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to www.bonbast.com and/or other sites on the Internet.  
 Users may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads) and other advertising service providers listed below. 

You can turn off certain third party cookies for advertising purposes by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative, located here: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/> or the DAA opt-out program, which are located here: <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>, here (for EU/EEA citizens): <http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/> and here (for mobile devices): <http://www.aboutads.info/appchoices>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include .... Google Adsense 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.bonbast.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. www.bonbast.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.bonbast.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

#### Third-party vendors and ad networks which serving ads on our mobile App:

#### Third-party vendors and ad networks which serving ads on our website

You may visit these websites (or alternatively by visiting: [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/)) to opt out of the use of cookies for personalized advertising
